# John A. Jacobs

Driven by a challenge, a full-stack web developer with a background in science, methodical problem solving, and varied life and work experience. Adept in all stages of development and ability to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

Atlanta, GA (423) 497-4941

john.a.jacobs1973@gmail.com

GitHub: GopherEverett

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/john-a-jacobs

#### RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

**RevHeads** — **React.js front-end/ Django back-end App** Web utilizing Django RESTful framework and React.js client-side rendering.

**Hangman** — Web Application Game

Static web app utilizing HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

RoastMe - Full-stack MEHN Web App

Full-stack server application; MongoDB/Mongoose for database management and Node/Express framework.

ATLive - Full-Stack MERN Web App

React Web App utilizing MongoDB, Node/Express.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Niedlov's Breadworks, Chattanooga, TN — Bench Supervisor

JUNE 2018 - JANUARY 2019

Supervised the production team in an artisanal bakery. Instrumental in maintaining a positive and productive work environment through training.

### ${\bf Macon\ County\ Commission,\ Macon\ County,\ AL-Maintenance}$

JULY 2016 - JULY 2017

Oversaw maintenance of countywide properties and facilities.

#### State Of Alabama, Montgomery, AL — Commissary Supervisor

OCTOBER 2008 - MARCH 2013

Oversaw sales, ordering, and inventory ensuring 100% availability of retail items.

#### **SKILLS**

Languages & Frameworks: Python, JavaScript, jQuery, Node, Express, React, AJAX, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

Management & Deployment: Git, GitHub, Heroku, Command Line

**Databases:** SQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB

#### **COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT**

**Omicron Delta Kappa:** National Leadership Honors Society

**Beta Beta Beta:** National Biology Honors Society

**Psi Chi:** National Psychology Honors Society

#### **EDUCATION**

## General Assembly, Atlanta, GA — Web Development Immersive

JANUARY 2019 - APRIL 2019

12 week/500-hour immersive study in full-stack web development.

#### Jacksonville State University, Jacksonville, AL — B.S. Biology

SEPTEMBER 1991 - MAY 1996

Received B.S. in Biology with a minor in Chemistry while involved in Microbiology research.